[ED].
I'm not sure, but I'll do my best.
It's a pig, so it's pork, right?
Meat and onions, right?
Carrots?
Is it big? I thought of it as a garnish.
I wonder how many slices of carrot would be good.
I wonder if it's okay to cut it like this.
It's a little bit of a mess. I wonder how many slices it should be. It looks kind of oily, so let's do it this way.
What is it? Ah!
Excuse me. Is it deep-fried? I imagine there's some kind of batter on it.
Won't it have an egg flavor?
I'm worried about that too.
That's a lot of meat.
I'll put it in at the end.
We look like a big family.
Oh, no, it's too much!
Oh, no!
Soy sauce!
Maybe some mirin (sweet cooking rice wine)
Three tablespoons.
Maybe 3 tablespoons.
No, 2.5.
[fast forward]
Is this sweet-and-sour pork?
Maybe not enough sugar.
Add potato starch.
It looks like it, but I can't taste it.
It doesn't taste right. Maybe there's not enough water.
That's 10 servings.
Is it okay?
I'm HIMEDA.
I put a lot of energy into getting dressed in short sleeves.
I think I can make it.
I'll do my best.
Sweet-and-sour pork?
Pork, right?
Which one is it?
Let's try this one.
Sweet and sour pork.
I'll add some vegetables.
I don't know. I don't know which one.
Let's try that one. Onions.
Orchestration
Orchestration.
Councillor.
Oh, my God.
dee
otesu
Ah-ha!
I'm going to bake it, for now.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Didn't we do this yesterday?
I'll fry it anyway.
What's "sundried eggs"?
It's different.
It's not what I expected.
It's like grilled meat.
Shall we add some vinegar?
Vinegar?
It's starting to look like something.
Maybe it's potato starch.
Oh, what should I do?
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Maybe I made a mistake...
katakuriko
potato starch
I'll try to unravel something.
Vinegar, vinegar, vinegar...
It's hardened.
Doesn't it look like it's getting a bit sticky?
No, it's just... it's stuck.
I don't know.
Is it close?
The moisture's gone.
Did it have red in it?
I'll do red.
I'll do both hands, and maybe it'll be done.
Oh, but it looks delicious.
Mmm-hmm.
It's done.
It's gratin.
Gratin.
Gratin
Gratin is probably this for now, right?
Put this in for the time being.
Yes, this is what we do.
Next.
Maybe with cheese.
Gratin has corn, right?
Onions.
I don't like carrots, so I'll leave them out.
I'll put whatever you like. Maybe just one portion here.
Okay, but onions are very tight.
That's why I don't like to cut them.
Cut it.
Oh!
When I cut onions, I make sure I never suck the naked meaning.
Then I really don't cry anymore, though.
Eh, why - oh no, it's starting to stain.
I've had enough, let's get on with it.
Well, speed is important. Speed is important.
I don't know.
You never burn potatoes, do you?
Good job.
What?
The onions aren't cut.
Look, it's like a sense.
Oh, no.
Is this plastic?
Let's just put a bunch of white stuff in there.
Yes, it's white.
If we put white stuff in, we can do this.
Oh!
It smells like stew.
I feel like gratin.
Gratin is done! It looks 100 points.
It's 100 points. The taste is probably fine too.
Spring Rolls
Spring rolls. But I've probably done this before when I was in kindergarten.
Wait, spring rolls.
What do you use? I don't know what's in it.
Oh, there's vermicelli in it. There's vermicelli in it, right? That's what's in the vermicelli soup. Maybe.
Where's the bamboo shoots? What is this? Does it look like bamboo shoots? This.
But the problem starts from here. I don't know what's going to happen next.
For now, I think I'll just cut it off. Vegetables.
What should I do? How many pieces should I cut?
But once.
Why don't I cut it like this?
But it's not this thick.
It's not this thick.
I'd like to shred something more.
I'll just have to work on it myself.
How do you cut bamboo shoots?
I want to shred it.
But I'll lose daylight if I do it this way.
I'm sorry for going this way and that way.
But I've never cut green peppers either.
Bell peppers...
What do I do with the seeds?
Seeds... we'll have to put them in one bell pepper at a time.
Wait, wait, wait, I'll wash them.
I'll wash these.I'll wash these.
I'm sorry about the seeds.
Hey, wait, what do you want me to do?
Can we just calm down for a second?
The problem is how to fold them.
The problem is how to fold it.
But it doesn't matter.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
And now this.
Oh! I want it to boil.
That's a little tricky, isn't it?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I wonder if it's okay.
It's impossible.
It's already on high heat.
Oh, my God.
You want some? Say "sizzle" for me, for God's sake.
Wow! It's done, it's done, it's done.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Wait!
Now I can get rid of the image that I don't cook for my fans
Now I can be like a cooking character!
That's great! You can do it!
Wait, that's it! That's it!
Hot, hot, hot!
I didn't make it.
That's it!
Aah! Wait! It's done!
Spring rolls are ready!
They smell a little burnt.
I think they taste really good!